Guide to the National Council of Jewish Women, Pittsburgh Section Records, 1894-2011 AIS.1964.40
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Political Action, 1929-1979; XI.
  - Human Relations Commission, 4.
    - Pennsylvania Program for Women and Girl Offenders, Inc., job opportunities section, and Concentrated Employment Program (CEP) (Box 35, Folder 18)
- Jewish Affiliations, 1928-1975; XII.
  Series XII contains materials for the Pittsburgh Section's Jewish affiliations. The NCJW Pittsburgh Section has been involved in many local, national, and international Jewish affairs. They have also founded institutions (Columbia School-IKS), participated in the founding of others (Conference of Jewish Women's Organizations), and have provided support for many more.
  The Jewish Organizations subseries contains information on the Community Relations Committee, at one time the Joint Public Relations Committee; the Jewish Public Relations Council; the Jewish Community Relations Council (JCRC); the Irene Kaufmann Settlement; the United Jewish Fund; and the Federation of Jewish Philanthropies. For more information on the JCRC the researcher should refer to the Papers of Lillian A. Friedberg (ais 2000:04)on deposit with the Archives Service Center. Friedberg served as Executive Director of the JCRC from 1943 to 1965.
  Also in this series are materials regarding the Expanded Overseas Program, the Israel Education Project, Seymour Fox Operation, Soviet Jewry programs, workshops and training, Community Leadership Training Program (CLTP), and information on the Evening and South Hills Branches.
  - Affiliations, 1.
    - American Jewish Committee, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - American Jewish Conference, 1943-1947 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1934-1946 (Box 36, Folder 4-7)
    - B'nai Brith, 1934-1955 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Irene Kaufmann Settlement (IKS), 1948-1958 (Box 36, Folder 9-14)
    - Community Relations Committee, 1943-1973 (Box 36, Folder 15-23)
    - Jewish Family and Children's Services, 1954-1963 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Social Service Bureau, 1938-1947 (Box 37, Folder 2-5)
    - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service, 1959 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Pittsburgh Conference of Federation of Jewish Women's Organizations, 1942-1946 (Box 37, Folder 7-11)
    - United Jewish Federation (UJF), 1940-1958 (Box 37, Folder 12-15)
    - Combined Young Men and Women's Hebrew Association and Irene Kaufmann Center Senior Citizens Clubs publications, "News and Views", April-May, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Young Men and Women's Hebrew Association, 1943-1957 (Box 37, Folder 17-22)
  - Expanded Overseas Program, 2.
    - Committee reports and memos, 1946-1971 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Books for Israel project, 1953 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Council Homes in Athens and Paris, 1946-1950 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Israel bonds, 1952-1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Israel education project, 1946-1971 (Box 38, Folder 5-9a)
    - Jewish National Funds Certificate #D17327, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Scholarships for overseas students, 1947-196(?) (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
    - Share-A-Toy project, 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Ship-A-Box project, 1949-1971 (Box 38, Folder 14-16)
    - Soviet Jewry programs, 1964-1975 (Box 38, Folder 17-22)
    - United Nations Association of Pittsburgh, 1945-1958 (Box 39, Folder 1-6)
    - United Nations General Assembly reports of NCJW accredited observer, 1948-1949 (Box 39, Folder 7-8)
    - United Nations Institutes (annual Eleanor Roosevelt UN Institutes) reports, 1961, 1963-1964 1968 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration (UNNRA), 1944 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Women's Action Committee for Lasting Peace, 1946-1950 (Box 39, Folder 11-15)
    - World Affairs Forums, Foreign Policy Association, 1953-1969 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - World Affairs Forums, Foreign Policy Association, and Pittsburgh membership directory, 1946 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - Israeli Friendship Committee (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Workshops and Training Institutes, 3.
    - Post Board Institute, 1948 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Workshop with Mrs. Robison, Executive Board workshop with Mrs. Cahn, April 1950 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
    - Training institute with Mrs. H. L. Levin, April 1951 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Group discussion technique, 1952 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Work conference in group leadership, 1956 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Workshop with Mrs. Hymes, November 1956 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Volunteer Training Institute, 1956-1959 (Box 40, Folder 8-11)
    - Board workshop with Mrs. Kreger, December 9, 1959 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Community Leadership Training Program (CLTP), 1958-1962 (Box 40, Folder 13-20)
    - Training consultations, 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Institute on Volunteer Training (held jointly with LHAS), 1966-1967 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Training institute for Chairmen, June 1971 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - Workshops on teenage behavior, 1954, 1956, 1967, 1971 (Box 40, Folder 24)
    - Management by Objective workshop, June 10, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 25)
    - Planning Today for Impact Tomorrow Board workshop, May 1975 (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Self-studies, Questionnaires, and Evaluations, 4.
    - Survey of Social Service Department, Pittsburgh section,; Survey of sewing groups and the need of such groups, February 1932 1932? (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Survey of the Pittsburgh section of NCJW, 1943? (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Survey of Council affiliations, 1944 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Survey of report on the NCJW by Sidney Hook, 1 volume (printed in, Strictly Confidential, Not for Publication) (Limited Access), 1946 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Reevaluation of present structure of NCJW Pittsburgh section, 1950 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Self-evaluation, reports, correspondence, questionnaires, and membership information forms, anonymous, 1952 (Box 41, Folder 6-9)
    - Questionnaires and analysis on section response and use of material provided by NCJW, 1954 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Completed questionnaires (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Annual questionnaire, completed questionnaires, and correspondence, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
    - Interim report of the Special Committee to evaluate the structure of the Pittsburgh section, February 28, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Special committee to study the role of NCJW in the general and Jewish community, summary of trends, October 2, 1956 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Koffee Klass questionnaire, September 1958 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Questionnaire on civil rights, January 9, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Questionnaires on community service, and, January 24, 1968, December 16, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Evaluation and Survey Committee report, April 11, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Questionnaire for section Board on issue of Vietnam, May 4, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Councilette and Teenage Branch, 5.
    - By-laws, rules, policies, and procedures, 1957-1961 undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Reports, 1954-1958, 1960-1961 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1948-1955 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1969 (Box 42, Folder 4-7)
    - Programs and invitations (most undated) (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - List of officers and members (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Councilette questionnaires (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - "The Councilette Advisor" by Mrs. Lewis Gordon, May 3, 1948 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Counciletter, 1953-1959, undated (Box 42, Folder 12-13)
    - Councilette publications, 1944-1963 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Juniors and Women, Ages 18-21, 6.
    - By-laws, Junior Branch, and Junior Division, undated (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Reports, 1928, 1947-1948, 1950-1956, undated (Box 42, Folder 16-17)
    - Financial reports, 1949-1954 (Box 42, Folder 18-19)
    - Board meeting minutes, 1947-1951 (Box 42, Folder 20-21)
    - Correspondence, 1938-1962 (Box 42, Folder 22-23)
    - Programs, 1948-1960, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - List of officers and members (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Junior questionnaire, 1952 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - The Torch, 1950-1959 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - National News, "Inside Junior Council", January 1951; April 1951 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Junior Councilette Merger, 1946-1952 (Box 43, Folder 6-9)
    - Evening Branch/Division
      - Policies and by-laws, A Guide for Branches (Box 43, Folder 10)
      - Minutes, 1945-1972 (Box 43, Folder 11-17)
      - Reports, 1945-1971 (Box 43, Folder 18-20)
      - Financial Reports, 1949-1953, 1967-1969 (Box 43, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, 1946-1965 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      - Programs, invitations, and cards (Box 44, Folder 2)
      - Lists of officers and members (Box 44, Folder 3)
      - Questionnaire (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - "Evening News" Issue I, September 1970 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - South Hills Branch By-laws; revisions, Rules of Procedure, job definition of a President, 1962; 1971; 1961 (Box 44, Folder 6)
      - Reports, 1955-1971 (Box 44, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, 1950-1963 (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - Programs, invitations, and cards (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Lists of officers and members (Box 44, Folder 10)
      - Questionnaires (Box 44, Folder 11)
      - South Hills Notes, intermittent (Box 44, Folder 12-14)
      - By-laws, revisions, Rules for Procedure for sections with divisions of the NCJW, 1958-1966 (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Organizational structure, plans, proposals, and charts, 1943-1960 (Box 44, Folder 16-17)
      - Divisional plan recommendations and reports, 1960, 1962, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, 1961-1967, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - President's Council, 1963-1967 (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - Meetings and workshops, 1962-1963 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Membership count and dues sheet, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 22)
      - Evening Division, 1962-1974, undated (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Division Five ("Points East Post"), minutes, reports, and programs, 1962-1970 (Box 45, Folder 2-4)
      - Division Six (Squirrel Hill West), reports, programs, and lists of officers and members, 1965-1968 (Box 45, Folder 5-7)
      - Division Seven (Box 45, Folder 8)
      - Division Eight (Squirrel Hill East), reports, programs, lists of officers and members, and newsletter, 1963-1968 (Box 45, Folder 9-12)
      - Triangle Division, reports, programs, lists of officers, and newsletter, 1964-1970 (Box 45, Folder 13-16)
  - Publications, 7.
    - Columbian Council of Jewish Women, Pittsburgh and Allegheny section, 1904-1906 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Council of Jewish Women, Greater Pittsburgh section, 1906-1908 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
    - Council of Jewish Women, Greater Pittsburgh section, 1924-1928 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Council of Jewish Women, Greater Pittsburgh Section, 1920-1921 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - NCJW Pittsburgh Section (combined with Monthly Bulletin), 1924-1960 (Box 46, Folder 6-8)
  - Volumes, 8.
    - Volumes 5-15, November 1927-June 1937 (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Volumes 16-18, January 1938-September 1939 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Volumes 27-33, January 1946-June 1952 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Volumes 34-35, November 1952-May 1956 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Volumes 36-37, December 1954-May 1956 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Volumes 38-42, October 1956-October 1961 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Council News, 9.
    - Volumes 1-3, December 1961-June 1965 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Volumes 3-5, October 1965-June 1967 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Volumes 6-8, October 1967-June 1970 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Volumes 9-10, September 1970-July 1972 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Volume 11, #1-#9, September 1972-June 1973 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Volume 12, #1-#7 (Volume 12 #1 should be volume 13), September 1973-May 1975 (Box 47, Folder 12-13)
    - Volume 13, #1; Volume 14, #8, March 1976 May 1977 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Volume 15, #1, ;Volume 16, #2-8, September 1977 June 1977 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Volume 17, #1,; Volume 17, #7, September-October 1979 June 1980 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Volume 18, #1-#18, September 1980-June 1981 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Volume 19, #1,; Volume 20, September 1981 June 1983 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - What's Happenin', Summer 1977, Summer 1978 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Affiliation Networks, 1896-1979; XIII.
  Series XIII: The NCJW Pittsburgh Section is part of a number of affiliated networks, including the Pennsylvania State Conference (sometimes called Pennsylvania Regional), the Central District, and the National Council. This series contains information on Central District Conferences, Pennsylvania State Conferences, NCJW, and the International Council of Jewish Women. Also included are materials on the NCJW Oral History Project, including awards, certificates, photographs, and "Bridges to History", a 26 minute film written and produced in 1980 by Marcia Frumerman and Gene Dickman to explain the NCJW Pittsburgh section Oral History Project.
  - Pennsylvania State Conferences, 1.
    - By-laws and amendments, 1927-1965 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
    - Officers, 1947-1965 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh regional conferences, 1939-1947 (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
    - State conferences, Pittsburgh, 1947-1954 (Box 48, Folder 6-13)
    - Pennsylvania regional conferences, 1955-1966 (Box 48, Folder 14-20)
  - Central District Conferences, 2.
    - Guidelines for implementation of Council's district organization, March 1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Conventions, Akron, 1968-1978 (Box 49, Folder 2-5a)
  - National Council of Jewish Women, 3.
    - By-laws, amendments, and resolutions, 1920-1979 (Box 49, Folder 6-17)
    - Committee on By-laws and Rules reports and correspondence, 1945-1968 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Guide to Action and Study of Resolutions, 1953-1957 (Box 49, Folder 19-20)
    - Correspondence, National section, 1931-1974 (Box 50, Folder 1-17)
    - Proceedings from first convention, and New Orleans, 1896, 1935 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh, 1938 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - New York City, 1940 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Dallas, 1946 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Baltimore, 1949 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Cleveland, 1953 (Box 51, Folder 6-16)
    - New Orleans, 1954-1955 (Box 51, Folder 17-21)
    - Washington, D.C., 1957 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Los Angeles, 1958-1959 (Box 52, Folder 1-5)
    - Pittsburgh, 1958-1961 (Box 52, Folder 6-8)
    - Minneapolis, 1963 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - New York City, 1962-1965 (Box 52, Folder 10-15)
    - Atlanta, 1967 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Chicago, 1969 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Miami, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - New York, 1977 (Box 52, Folder 18b)
    - Dallas, 1979 (Box 52, Folder 18c)
    - Miscellaneous, discharge of employees, and union problems, 1947 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Activity Cues, 1958-1971 (Box 53, Folder 1-2)
    - Aids for Council leadership, 1953-1958 (Box 53, Folder 3-5)
    - "The Ballad of Carrie, the Constant Woman,", 1959 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Budget materials (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Catalogues of NCJW materials, 1968, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Community services projects, Community services manual, 1953; 1957 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Contemporary Jewish Affairs, 194? (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Council publicity guides, 1939-1968 (Box 53, Folder 11-11a)
    - Good Council Neighbors, Outreach Services for the Older Adults, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Council Programs for the Jewish Holidays, 1958 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Democracy is You: Due It Now (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Election kit, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Service to Foreign Born Materials (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - A Half Century of Social Action: How to Publish a Telephone Directory and Have you met the Woman of the Year?, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Membership materials, 1945-1971 (Box 53, Folder 18-19)
    - News releases, 1955-1956 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Council in the News and Across the Nation, 1960-1962 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - News for Publicity Chairman, 1966-1973 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Overseas programs (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - PR: The Larger View (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Pre-school materials (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Public Affairs, January 1954-April 1956 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Rehabilitation for Living, 1962 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - School for Community Action V, 1969 (Box 54, Folder 8-9)
    - Social Legislation: Social Welfare (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Thrift Shop Ideas (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Ways and Means, miscellaneous, 1955-1968 (Box 54, Folder 12-13)
    - Council Leader, Council News, and Council Platform, (intermittent), 1958-1971 (Box 54, Folder 14-16)
    - The Council Woman, 1946-1966 (Box 54, Folder 17-18)
    - The Lifeline, 1950 (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - NCJW Journal, Newsletter, Spotlight, Washington Newsletter, (intermittent), 1935-1979 (Box 55, Folder 1-8)
  - International Council of Jewish Women, 4.
    - International Council of Jewish Women (Box 55, Folder 8a-9)
    - Publications and procedures of other NCJW branches, 1947-1958 (Box 55, Folder 10-11)
    - Yearbook, Montreal,; Philadelphia, 1952, 1909-1910 (Box 55, Folder 12-13)
    - Awards and certificates, 1946-1966 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Awards correspondence, 1946-1972 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Photographs (Box 55, Folder 16-22b)
    - Miscellaneous membership lists, and souvenir program, 1910 (Box 55, Folder 23-25)
  - Oral History Project, 5.
    - Oral History Project, "Bridges to History" and tape recording (Box 55, Folder 1-2)
    - Type-high cuts (7 assorted sizes) (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Type-high cuts/half tone (41 assorted sizes) (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Photocopies of scrapbook clippings, 1952-1958 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
    - 1924-1926 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 1928 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 1929-1930 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 1931-1932 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - 1932-1933 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 1936-1938 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 1939-1943 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 1943-1944 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - 1945-1947 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - 1946 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - 1956-1957 (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Early history, assembled in, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- Photographs, Scrapbooks, and Record Books, 1960-1973; XIV.
  Series XIV contains photographs, scrapbooks, and record books for a number of the Pittsburgh Section's activities for the period 1960 to 1973. The Angel Ball, sometimes called the Angel Ball Cotillion, is the bulk of the photographs for this series. Although there is a volume "Friends of Anathan House," this is simply a list of contributors to Anathan House at their dedication in 1963 - there are no photographs in this volume. The researcher should also be aware that Box 60 also contains slides and negatives for the same years.
  - Slides of Council Care I and II and Children's Waiting Room (Box 60, Volume 1)
  - Negatives of By Myself I'm A Book and reception for book, 1972 (Box 60, Volume 2)
  - Angel Ball, March 25, 1967 (Box 60, Volume 3)
  - Angel Ball Cotillion, 1964 (Box 60, Volume 4)
  - Angel Ball Cotillion, 1960-1963 (Box 60, Volume 5)
  - Angel Ball, 1969 (Box 60, Volume 6)
  - Angel Ball, May 11, 1968 (Box 60, Volume 7)
  - Friends of Anathan House, 1963 (Box 60, Volume 8)
  - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings, 1950-1951 (Box 61, Volume 1)
  - Anathan House activities, 1970-1973 (Box 61, Volume 2)
  - Angel Ball, 1970 (Box 61, Volume 3)
  - "Energy and NCJW," slide and matching cassette description of NCJW Pittsburgh Section (Box 61, Volume 4)
  - Record book of membership and contributors, 1947-1956 (Box 61, Volume 5-10)
- Publications and Organizational Records, 1959-1987; XV.
  Series XV contains publications and organizational records for the NCJW Pittsburgh Section. Of interest in this series is a catalog listing English language books relating to Judaism, including author, title, publisher, and number of pages. However, this catalog was completed in 1974, so titles published after this date are not included in their list. The organizational records contain various materials including meeting minutes and national by-laws, policies, and procedures.
  - Field Research Kit for Mothers in the Workplace, 1986 (Box 62, Volume 1)
  - 37th National Convention for Women in Power, March 19-22, 1987 (Box 62, Volume 2)
  - The Jewish Family: Evolution or Revolution, 1982 (Box 62, Volume 3)
  - Working Papers on Long-term Care, October 1981 (Box 62, Volume 3)
  - Research Institute for Innovation in Education, Report on Research and Activities, No. 8, 1985-1987 (Box 62, Volume 4)
  - Data Report to the Police-Community Relations Project, September 1972 - July 1973 (Box 62, Volume 5)
  - Friends Indeed, Volunteer Resource Manual, October 1987 (Box 62, Volume 6)
  - English Language Titles of Judaica, August 1974 (Box 62, Volume 7)
  - Lifestyle Project, 1975-1978 (Box 62, Folder 1-2)
  - Board meeting agendas, September 10, 1974 - April 6, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence from National, 1966-1970 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Meeting minutes, June 12, 1974 - March 14, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 5-7)
  - National by-laws, policies, and procedures, 1959-1977 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Shop-CETA City Grant, 1978-1981 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Shop-CETA County #1, 1977-1979 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Shop employees and work records, 1978-1981 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Shop-CETA County #3, 1980-1981 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Washington Institute, February 16-18, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Subject Files, 1943-1995; XVI.
  Series XVI contains files for a range of subjects. Because these boxes were added to the collection later than 1964, many of the subjects in this series also have materials located throughout the collection. All files are alphabetically arranged. Material added in 2011 can be found under the section "New Material Added."
  - Abortion Rights (Pro Choice), 1980-1989 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Adult Day Care, Council Care Project, 1980-1983 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Anathan House, 1964-1988 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Annual Meeting minutes, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Annual National Support, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Annual Support Campaign, 1985-1986 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Annual Support, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Area 12 Institute, 1969, 1972-1973, 1977-1982 (Box 63, Folder 16-17)
  - Banners, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Board minutes, 1975-1985 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Board training, 1980-1987 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Breast cancer awareness, 1995 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - "Bridges to History", 1981 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1983-1984 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Central District Convention, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Central District Convention, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Central District Convention, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Central District Convention, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Central District Conference, 1986 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Central District Conference, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Central District Conference, 1988 (Box 63, Folder 30-31)
  - Central District Conference, 1991 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Central District newsletter, 1969-1986 (intermittent) (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Central District questionnaire, 1984-1991 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Central District Representative, 1973-1989 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Central District skit, 1984 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Central District training, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Challenge, 1988-1993 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Children's Waiting Room, 1990-1995 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Civil Rights Restoration Act, 1985 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Community Newsdate, 1986-1992 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Council Care, 1983 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Council Care, 1984-1985 (Box 64, Folder 1)